Whenever Zionism and the doctrines of Zionism was taught to you in church, it always comes with Islamophobia.
The two have to go hand in hand because in order to portray the state of Israel as the victims of an evil force oppressing them,
you have to create the boogeyman that's doing it, which they say is Islam.
So when I arrived on my dorm floor, ironically, the majority of the dorm floor were Palestinian Muslim dudes.
Very vocal, joking, talking loud, smoking hookah with their dorm door open, right?
And just being that kid, I walked right into the door and I said, hey, what's up, you terrorist motherfuckers?
First thing I said, and it was about five dudes.
Some of them thought it was kind of funny.
And, you know, like you would think a lot of them would just want to, you know, whoop my ass.
And I'm sure some of them did, but at the same time, they're just so bewildered that this guy did that.
So immediately they were curious, like, who is this guy?
So I sat down and, you know, smoked hookah with them.
They offered me hummus, all that.
We just got right into it.
Ripped the Band-Aid off, started arguing.
I started spewing all the propaganda bullshit that I had been taught in church.
Everything, all the cleats, everything you hear as your typical Zionist says today, that was me.
I was that guy spewing it out.
And they said, Mark, Mark, you dumb shit.
And everything I said, every point of propaganda, every point of dogma that I was taught,
they just swatted it like mosquitoes out of the sky.
Three hours.
We're talking about years of propaganda just deprogrammed.
That was the connection right there I had with Palestine.
And it could have gone any other way.
They could have assigned me to any other dorm floor and dorm room.
I always reflect on that, that it was just one number that determined my fate for the rest of my life.